# **Candice Weaver – Front-End Developer**

**Github:** github.com/CandiceWeaver **Website:** https://candiceweaver.dev

# **Professional Profile**

I am a confident individual seeking a role in the IT industry. From managing my workload and using my own initiative in a recent customer service role, I was able to exceed my target and provide complete customer satisfaction. I am currently looking for my first role as a developer, where I can improve my skills and gain work experience.

# Career Summary

# April 2021 - Present Astute, Bournemouth Business Development Specialist

#### Outline

Astute is a telemarketing agency that works on behalf of various other companies. My role here was to sell digital solutions to existing customers on behalf of an international company.

Key Responsibilities

- To reach a daily target of at least 3 sales per day
- To act as a representative of the company I act on behalf of
- To understand the needs of the customers to match them with a suitable product
- To understand the products I am selling and the benefits of them
- To communicate effectively with customers over the phone

## February 2020 – October 2020 CEGA, Christchurch Customer Service Advisor

#### Outline

CEGA is a travel insurance services company that works on behalf of travel insurance companies as their claims and assistance services. My role here was to register and assess the claims they receive and to support their customers throughout the claims process.

## Key Responsibilities

- To deliver exceptional customer service and support to our customers, even during busy periods
- To liaise between our customer and the underwriters of the insurance policies
- To assess cover for insurance claims and make payments to the policy holders
- To understand the requirements of our customers to better understand their claims
- To keep up to date with industry knowledge to provide customers with correct information
- To communicate effectively using different forms of communication, such as over the phone and email
- To resolve any complaints that arise by following CEGA's procedures and the procedures of the insurance companies we work on behalf of

# Key Achievements:

I consistently completed over 20 claims each day throughout the 8 months I worked here

### **Pastry Chef**

#### Outline

The Chewton Glen is a luxury boutique hotel that puts its guests at the heart of its business. My role here was as a pastry chef.

### Key Responsibilities

- To maintain excellent health and safety standards
- To communicate effectively with both my department and other departments within the hotel
- To efficiently organise my workload
- To adapt quickly to new challenges
- To support management with the training of new staff
- To exceed the guests' expectations
- To utilise my knowledge as a chef to meet our guests' requirements, such as food allergies or food preferences

#### Key Achievements

- I regularly prepared food for events at the hotel, for which numbers often exceeded 100 people
- I prepared buffet food for a Children In Need event, for which we catered for over 200 guests

## February 2017 – October 2018 The Pig, Brockenhurst Apprentice Chef

#### Outline

The Pig is a boutique hotel in the heart of The New Forest. My role here was as an apprentice chef and I acquired many useful skills here, which can be transferred to other roles.

### Key Responsibilities

- To prepare food to a high standard
- To maintain a high standard of health and safety
- To communicate effectively within my department

#### Key Achievements

- I prepared food for The Catey's, which is an important awards event for the hospitality industry
- I regularly prepared and served food for over 150 guests in a single service period

### August 2016 – February 2017 Tesco, New Milton Customer Assistant

My job at Tesco was my most recent customer facing role prior to becoming a chef. A few of the most important tasks that were given to me were ensuring the products we sold were of good quality and proactively informing customers about the products and services they were interested in. Therefore, I took pride in providing complete customer satisfaction.

# **Education and Qualifications**

- The Open University | February 2019 Present Business Management
- Brockenhurst College | September 2014 July 2016
   2 AS Levels and 2 A Levels
- Highcliffe Secondary School | September 2009 July 2014
   13 GCSEs

# References available on request